{
    "id": "56f80e7e943d4142b1d5f9636ae10cdc",
    "title": "Formation of questions and negatives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "836b3c210d0f4f1abd53e67befc153ae",
            "title": "Formation of Negatives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Martha ................... not live with her sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "James ......................... not own three cars.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cats ................... not chase mice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Birds ................... not make their nests in trees.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Deciduous trees ...................... not shed their leaves in autumn.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The earth ........................ not move around the sun.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Honey ........................... not taste sweet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandparents ..................... not keep pigs in their shed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ....................... not work hard to support his family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Opposite poles ..................... not attract.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}